<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!--
    Copyright (c) 2012 SunGard CSA LLC and others.
    All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials
    are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0
    which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
    http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html
   
    Contributors:
       SunGard CSA LLC - initial API and implementation and/or initial documentation
 -->

<cheatsheet title="Running the Workflow with Different Variable Values">
  <intro>
    <description>
		This cheat sheet guides you through the process of running a
		workflow depending on different values of a configuration variable.
	</description>
   </intro>
  <item
        skip="true"
        title="Starting the Process in the Portal" 
         href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/config-var/tut-config-var-prod.html#run">
     <description>
        <br/>
	1. Start your server and deploy the model.<br/>
	2. Start the Process Portal.<br/>
	3. Login as administrator with motu/motu.<br/>
	4. Switch to the <b>Participant Management</b> View of the <b>Administration Perspective</b>.<br/>
	5. Create a user and assign him to the role we added to the model.<br/>
	6. Logout and login again as the newly created user.<br/>
 	</description>
 	</item>
  <item
        skip="true"
        title="Running the Workflow in Test Mode"
        href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/config-var/tut-config-var-prod.html#runTest">
     <description>
        <br/>
	1. In the <b>Workflow Perspective</b>, start the available process.<br/>
	2. Complete activity <b>Starting Activity</b>.<br/><br/>
	Per default, the model is run in test mode as the default value of the configuration variable is "TEST".
	Thus, the activity <b>Activity Production Only</b> is skipped and we see activity <b>Continue</b>. <br/>
 	</description>
 	</item>
  <item
        skip="true"
  		title="Switching to Production Mode"
        href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/config-var/tut-config-var-prod.html#prod"> 	
     <description>
		To run the model workflow in production mode, we change the value of our configuration variable to "PRODUCTION":<br/>
     1. Switch to the <b>Configuration Variables</b> view in the <b>Administration Perspective</b>. <br/>
     2. In the <b>Value</b> column, change the value of the variable to "PRODUCTION". <br/>
     3. Click the <b>Change</b> button in the upper right corner to save the new configuration variable value.<br/>
     4. Now start the process again.<br/>
     5. Complete activity <b>Starting Activity</b>.<br/><br/>
     The transition condition checks the value of the variable and decides to run the activity forseen for production. Thus, the next activity opening is activity <b>Activity Production Only</b>.<br/>
  	</description>
  </item>
</cheatsheet>
