<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!--
    Copyright (c) 2012 SunGard CSA LLC and others.
    All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials
    are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0
    which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
    http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html
   
    Contributors:
       SunGard CSA LLC - initial API and implementation and/or initial documentation
 -->

<cheatsheet title="Creating a Model with a Configuration Variable">
  <intro>
    <description>
    	This cheat sheet guides you through the steps of creating a model having
    	a configuration variable, which is used in a transition condition.</description>
  </intro>
  <item
        skip="true"
        title="Creating the Model"
         href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/config-var/tut-config-var-prod.html#createModel">
     <description>
        Create a model in a dynamic Web project:<br/>
	1. Create a dynamic Web project as described in the Support Case Cheat Sheet.<br/>
	2. Create a model <b>ProductionOrTestVarDemo</b>.<br/>
 	</description>
 	</item>
  <item
        skip="true"
        title="Adding the Configuration Variable"
         href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/config-var/tut-config-var-prod.html#add">
     <description>
        Add a configuration variable to your model:<br/>
	1. Open the model properties page.<br/>
	2. Click on <b>Configuration Variables</b>.<br/>
	3. Click <b>Add</b>.<br/>
	4. Click in the <b>Name</b> column and enter the variable name <b>Environment</b>.<br/>
	5. Enter <b>TEST</b> as default value in the <b>Default Value</b> column entry field.<br/>
	6. Optionally add a description.<br/>
 	</description>
 	</item>
  <item
        skip="true"
  	title="Creating the Workflow"
         href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/config-var/tut-config-var-prod.html#workflow">
     <description>
	Create the following workflow:<br/>
	1. Create a manual trigger followed by a manual activity <b>Starting Activity</b>.<br/>
	2. Right-click the activity and select <b>Split Behavior > XOR</b>.<br/>
	3. Create an activity <b>Activity Production Only</b>. This will be the activity to be performed in production mode only.<br/>
	4. Create another activity <b>Continue</b> to be performed after the production activity or from the starting activity directly.<br/>
	5. Add a role to the model and assign it as performer of all activities and the manual trigger.<br/>
	6. Create a connection from the split joint of activity <b>Starting Activity</b> to activity <b>Activity Production Only</b> and one to activity <b>Continue</b>.<br/>
   	</description>
  </item>
  <item
        skip="true"
  	title="Enter a Transition Condition"
         href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/config-var/tut-config-var-prod.html#workflow">
     <description>
	Enter a condition transition to the transition from the split joint to activity <b>Activity Production Only</b>:<br/>
	1. Double-click the transition in the diagram.<br/>
	2. In the transition condition property page dialog, enter the following Condition Expression:<br/>
	"${Environment}" == "PRODUCTION";<br/>
	3. Open the model property page and switch to the <b>Configuration Variable</b> section.<br/><br/>
	In the <b>References</b> part, the transition and its condition referencing to our <b>Environment</b> variable should be displayed.<br/>
   	</description>
  </item>
</cheatsheet>
