<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!--
    Copyright (c) 2012 SunGard CSA LLC and others.
    All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials
    are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0
    which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
    http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html
   
    Contributors:
       SunGard CSA LLC - initial API and implementation and/or initial documentation
 -->

<cheatsheet title="Creating a Provider Model">
  <intro>
    <description>
    	This cheat sheet will guide you through the steps of creating a provider model.</description>
  </intro>
  <item       
        skip="true"
        title="Creating the Workflow"
         href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/multi-model-env/create-provider-model.html">
     <description>
     <br/>
     Create a model <b>Provider</b> in a dynamic Web project with the following workflow:<br/>
     1. Create a manual trigger.<br/>
     2. Create a manual activity named <b>Collect Customer Information</b>.<br/>
     3. Create a subsequent application activity named <b>Send Notification Email</b>.<br/>
     4. Create a structured data <b>Customer Information</b>. Make sure the <b>Visibility Public</b> option is selected.<br/>
     5. Provide In and Out data mapping between the data and the manual activity.<br/>
     6. Similarly, create a structured data <b>Email Address</b>.<br/>
     7. Add the fields <b>Fromaddress</b> and <b>Toaddress</b>.<br/>
     8. Add an In data mapping from activity <b>Collect Customer Information</b>.<br/>
     9. Add an Out data mapping to activity <b>Send Notification Email</b>.<br/>
     10. Define a mail application and connect it to the <b>Send Notification Email</b> activity. Make sure that the <b>Visibility Public</b> option is selected.<br/>
     11. Define the Administrator as participant for the required elements in the model.<br/>
 	</description>
  </item>
  <item       
        skip="true"
        title="Defining a Process Interface"
         href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/multi-model-env/create-provider-model.html">
     <description>
     Now define the process interface:<br/>
     1. In the Outline View, double-click on process <b>Collect Customer Information</b> to open its property page.<br/>
     2. Click on <b>Process Interface</b> and select <b>Provider Process Interface</b> from the drop-down list.<br/>
     3. Click <b>Add</b> to define a <b>Formal Parameter 1</b> of the process interface.<br/>
     4. Select <b>INOUT</b> from the <b>Direction</b> drop-down list.<br/>
     5. Select <b>Customer Information</b> from the <b>Data Type</b> and <b>Data</b> drop-down lists.<br/>
     6. Click <b>Apply</b> and <b>OK</b>.<br/><br/>
     Now the provider model is ready and you can proceed with creating the consumer model.
 	</description>
  </item>
</cheatsheet>
