<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!--
    Copyright (c) 2011 SunGard CSA LLC and others.
    All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials
    are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0
    which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
    http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html
   
    Contributors:
       SunGard CSA LLC - initial API and implementation and/or initial documentation
 -->

<cheatsheet title="Creating a Consumer Model">
  <intro>
    <description>
    	This cheat sheet will guide you through the steps of creating a consumer model.</description>
  </intro>
  <item       
        skip="true"
        title="Creating a File Connection"
         href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/multi-model-env/create-consumer-model.html#fileConnection">
     <description>
     First, we create a file connection to the provider model:<br/>
	 1. Create a model named <b>Consumer.xpdl</b>.<br/>
     2. Right-click on the <b>External Model Information</b> in the Outline view and select <b>File Connection</b>.<br/>
     3. In the file connection drop-down list, browse to the path for the created provider model named <b>Provider</b>.<br/><br/>
     Once the file connection is established, the elements of the provider model that can be referenced are available under the created file connection in the Outline view.
  	</description>
  </item>
  <item       
        skip="true"
        title="Creating the Activities"
         href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/multi-model-env/create-consumer-model.html#referencing">
     <description>
     Now create the necessary activities for the workflow in the consumer model:<br/>
	 1. Create a manual trigger.<br/>
	 2. Create a manual activity named <b>CustEnquiry</b>.<br/>
	 3. Drag and drop the referenced process definition named <b>Collect Customer Information</b> from the connected file in the Outline view.<br/>
	 4. Connect all these activities.<br/>
	 5. Create two more manual activities named <b>Sanction Loan</b> and <b>Do not Sanction Loan</b>.<br/>
	 6. Define Administrator as the Participant for the required elements.<br/>
	</description>
  </item>
  <item       
        skip="true"
        title="Creating the Data and Data Mappings"
         href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/multi-model-env/create-consumer-model.html#referencing">
     <description>
     Now create the data and data mappings:<br/>
	 1. Create a primitive data named <b>LoanAmount</b> of integer type and provide it in the In Data Mapping for the <b>Sanction Loan</b> and <b>Do not Sanction Loan</b> activities.<br/>
	 2. Also, provide the <b>LoanAmount</b> in the Out Data Mappings of the <b>CustEnquiry</b> activity.<br/>
	 3. Drag and drop the <b>CustomerInformation</b> from the Outline view under the <b>File Connection</b> and rename it to <b>CustomerData</b>.<br/>
	 4. Double-click the <b>Collect Customer Information</b> activity.<br/>
	 5. Define the In Data Mapping in the <b>ProcessInterfaceContext</b> as <b>CustomerData</b> in the <b>Data</b> drop-down list and <b>Formal Parameter 1</b> as the Access Point.<br/>
	 6. Define the Out Data Mapping in the <b>ProcessInterfaceContext</b> as <b>CustomerData</b> in the <b>Data</b> drop-down list and <b>Formal Parameter 1</b> as the Access Point.<br/>
	</description>
  </item>
  <item       
        skip="true"
        title="Creating Transition Conditions"
         href="/org.eclipse.stardust.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/multi-model-env/create-consumer-model.html#referencing">
     <description>
     Create the transition conditions:<br/>
     1. Right-click the <b>Collect Customer</b> Information activity and select <b>Split Behavior &gt; XOR</b>.<br/>
     2. Create transitions to the activities <b>Sanction Loan</b> and <b>Do not Sanction Loan</b>.<br/>
	 3. Define a transition condition for the <b>Sanction Loan</b> activity with the following expression:<br/>
	  CustomerData.AssetSalaray &gt;10000 &amp;&amp; LoanAmount &lt;5000;<br/>
	 4. Also define the following transition condition for activity <b>Do not Sanction Loan</b>:<br/>
	 CustomerData.AssetSalaray&lt;=10000 &amp;&amp; LoanAmount&gt;=5000;<br/>
 	</description>
  </item>
</cheatsheet>
