<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2011 SunGard CSA LLC and others.
    All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials
    are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0
    which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
    http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html
   
    Contributors:
       SunGard CSA LLC - initial API and implementation and/or initial documentation
 -->

<cheatsheet title="Executing Workflow">
  <intro>
    <description>
    	This cheat sheet guides you through the process of executing your 
        workflow.</description>
  </intro>
  <item dialog="true" href="/ag.carnot.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/tut-main-13.htm#activityStart" 
  	title="Processing the Create Case Activity">
       <description> ACME can now execute their support case management process. 
  		To perform the activity <b>Create Case</b>:<br/><br/>
		1. Again go to the start URL of the Process Portal (&quot;http://hostname:port/Support-Case&quot;).<br/>
		2. Enter the ID and password of the newly created user and confirm with <b>Login</b>.<br/>
		3. Click <b>Support Case Management</b> under <b>My Startable Processes</b> to start the 
		  process.<br/>
		4. The GUI panel assigned to the <b>Create Case</b> activity opens in the view area to the right.<br/>
		5. Fill in the empty fields with appropriate information.<br/>
		6. Click the <b>Complete</b>button to complete the activity.<br/><br/> 
		The first activity of the process has been performed. 
	</description>
  </item>
  <item dialog="true" href="/ag.carnot.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/tut-main-13.htm#analyzeActivity" 
  	title="Start the Analyze To Solve Activity">
       <description> A work item for this activity will be placed in the worklist of the user 
       assigned to the role <b>Engineer</b>.<br/><br/>
       1. Log on to the Stardust Process Portal with the ID and password of the user assigned 
       to the role <b>Engineer</b>.<br/>
       2. In the <b>Worklist by Role</b> click on <b>Engineer</b>.<br/>
       3. In the worklist of pending activities appears, choose one.<br/><br/>
	</description>
	</item>
  <item dialog="true" href="/ag.carnot.docs.dev/html/handbooks/tutorial/tut-main-13.htm#analyzeActivity" 
  	title="Complete the Process">
       <description>
       Now the work appears with the data from the previous activity in view.
       The Output Data Mappings in the process definition added two new output items for this 
       activity, <b>State</b> and <b>Analysis</b>.<br/><br/>
       1. Entering a "C" for the state variable would send the item to the <b>Deliver Patch</b> 
         user activity (CLOSED path).<br/>
       2. Entering an "R "for the state variable would send the item to the 
         <b>Notify Customer</b> (REJECTED path).
	</description>
	<onCompletion>Congratulations! You have completed the Stardust Developers Support Case Tutorial</onCompletion>
  </item>
</cheatsheet>
